This entire pint of cherry garcia ice
cream packs over 30 gram of protein for
under 300 calories. Let me show you how
to make it. Starting off, you're going
to need some cherries. I use frozen
cherries. You can use fresh, whatever
you got. And then you're going to top
that with your sweetener, salt, and
zantham gum. And just shake that up and
let it merate for a few minutes. This
will help extract some of those juices
from the cherries and give it a way
better cherry flavor. And then you can
just top that with your protein shake.
Use a vanilla protein shake. You can
also use milk and protein powder if
that's what you got. Doesn't really
matter. Then we're going to freeze that
pint for at least 16 hours. Take it out,
run under hot water, and then throw it
in the Ninja Creamy on the light ice
cream setting. While that's spinning, we
can make our chocolate chips. And I know
what you're thinking. You already have
chocolate chips. Why are you making your
own? Well, I made a whole video about
this. These are way, way better. You
just take some chocolate chips, melt
that down with a little bit of coconut
oil and you get this rich velvety
chocolate syrup like substance and then
you throw that in the hole that you dig
out in the Ninja Creamy and it makes the
perfect chocolate chips. Dieting doesn't
have to be boring. You can literally eat
ice cream every single night